http://www.talespin.com/privacy-policy

CONTACTHomePlatformRunwayCoPilotPropelLearning ContentLeading Through UncertaintyEffective FeedbackXR for InsurancePlatformRunway PlatformCoPilot Virtual HumanPropel TrainingPlatformRunway PlatformCoPilot Virtual HumanPropel TrainingLearning ContentLeading Through UncertaintyEffective FeedbackXR for InsuranceVR Training StudyAbout UsNewsCareersContact UsBlogPrivacy Policy1. Acknowledgement and AcceptanceThis Privacy Policy is intended to describe how personal information is used and processed at Talespin’s website. Talespin is committed to protect your privacy. You can browse most of our site (http://talespin.company) without leaving any personal information, but sometimes we do need this kind of data to adequately respond to your requests. Talespin guarantees that our activities are kept within the confines of this Policy. Please read the complete Privacy Policy Statement carefully. By visiting and using http://talespin.company you accept the terms described below. Talespin reserves the right to modify this statement and terms of use in the whole or in part at any time without any additional notifications, so please check this Policy periodically.2. Site UsageNo visitor of this web site may distribute, exchange, modify, sell, or transmit any information published on this site, including but not limited to any text, images, audio or video, for any business or commercial purpose. The site cannot be used for or involved in illegal activity of any kind.3. Gathering and Using InformationWhen a visitor requests a page from(http://talespin.company, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. This information may include the IP address of the site that directed you to http://talespin.company, your IP address, operating system version and your web browser. This information reveals nothing personal about you and the practice of collecting such data is common for every web server on the Internet today. Talespin uses your IP address for the following purposes: Diagnose problems with our servers Administer our site (this data gives us the idea which parts of our site users are visiting more frequently)Investigate misuses of http://talespin.company We don’t link IP addresses to any personal data. This means that visitors of our site are tracked, but they remain anonymous.Contact forms at http://talespin.company require your name, e-mail and company name. We collect this information and use it for getting in touch with you only. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to any third party without your consent.4. Cookies Our site uses cookies – small files that contain identifiers sent from a web server to a browser and stored by the latter. The identifier is sent back to the server every time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies help us enhance your user experience of our web site by helping us monitor which pages of our web site you find useful and which you do not. Plus cookies allow us to optimize and serve the content (including but not limited to ads by Google) based on your past visits to our website. Cookies do not ever give us the access to your computer or to any data about you, other than the information you want to share with us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can modify your browser settings at any time to decline cookies. However, this may generally decrease your user experience and prevent you from taking full advantage of our web site.5. Security Our site has advanced security measures to prevent data loss, misuse or alteration. All your personal information resides behind a firewall, and access to it is restricted to most of Talespin personnel (excluding managers that communicate with you directly).6. Personal Information Disclosure Talespin may disclose your personal information when it is required by law or there are sufficient grounds to believe that this action is necessary to: Investigate unlawful activities or comply with legal process served on Talespin Protect and defend the rights or property of Talespin or visitors of http://talespin.company Identify persons violating the law, Talespin Privacy Policy or the rights of third parties  Reply to user requests7. Changes Talespin reserves the right to change, modify or otherwise update this Privacy Statement at any time. So we encourage you to review this privacy statement periodically to track the changes.8. Contact Information Talespin welcomes your comments and questions on this statement. Feel free to contact us at http://talespin.company  or via e-mail info@talespin.companyMenuAbout UsNewsCareersContact UsPrivacy PolicySOCIALFacebookTwitterInstagramLinkedInYouTubeGet the latest industry insights and news from Talespin:Thank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.Copyright © 2020 Talespin Reality Labs, Inc. All rights reserved.
